（你还活着）
伙计
Hey, boy.
你没事的
Oh, you're fine.
你没事
You are fine.
过来
Hey, come here.
你还活着
You… are alive.
格伦还没回来 我得陪着玛姬
Glenn's still not back. I need to be there for Maggie.
- 我说了不 - 卡尔
- I said no. - Carl.
你之前弄错了
Look, you were wrong before.
这地方不大 可以保护
This place isn't too big to protect.
你得留下防守
And you need to stay back and help protect it.
这里准备好了
This place is ready.
我们大部分人都训练过了 你知道的
Most of us have been trained, you know that.
如果你担心袭击 你根本不会走
If you were worried about an attack, you wouldn't be leaving.
你知道山顶寨有多远吗
You know how far the Hilltop is?
你知道可能发生什么吗
You know what could happen?
救世军就在外面
Those Saviors are out there.
你知道他们对丹妮斯做了什么
You know what they did to Denise,
他们想对玛姬和卡萝尔做什么
what they tried to do with Maggie and Carol,
还有达里尔 罗西塔和尤金
to Daryl, to Rosita, to Eugene.
你不能碰上这种事 好吗
That's not happening to you, all right?
我不允许
I'm not gonna let it.
有什么变化吗
Any change?
她的情况在恶化
She's getting worse.
车子选得不错
Good call on the transport.
我觉得她会更舒服
Well, I figured she'd be more comfortable.
也意味着能坐更多人
It also means you got room for more.
他们在外面 所以我要跟你去
They're out there, so I'm gonna be there with you.
我们要去
We are.
买一送一
Package deal.
我也是送的
Uh, what she said.
你想撞到他们 对吗
You want to run into them, right?
你希望他们会出现
You hope they show up.
天啊 重点是让玛姬看医生 不是…
Jesus, this is about getting Maggie to a doctor, not about…
去你的 我要去
Screw you, I'm going.
伊妮德 别 等等
Enid, stop. Just wait.
听着 路途遥远 而你刚…
Look, it's a long trip, and you're just getting over…
这只是表面擦伤
It's a superficial graze,
蛋白质在结合
proteins are binding,
而且我们得讨论弹药的生产
plus we need to discuss ammunition production.
和制造 所以走吧
and manufacture, so let's roll.
我已经试过了 他得寸进尺
I already tried. Give him an inch, he's taking a mile.
我只要求你给我点时间
I'm only asking for 23, give or take,
根据路线来定
depending on the route.
我知道我能帮忙
I know I can be of some help.
就是此时此刻了
Now's the time and here's the place.
别忽视我
Don't shine me.
我来做你的军师 我绝对会的
I'll be your anchorman. Yes, I damn will.
为什么是这种表情
Why the face?
希望你别怪罪我们
I hope you're not putting this on us.
我们给你们指了明路
I mean, we showed your people the way forward.
给你们定了规矩
We gave you rules.
你们违反了规矩就得死
You broke the rules, so folks had to die.
开第一枪的人
The one who fired the first shot,
我们吊死了他 以儆效尤
we strung him up to make an example of him.
事情本可以就此平息
It could've stopped there.
但你们还是不听
But you people still didn't listen.
想抵抗我们
You wanted to fight us.
所以只能这样了
So this is how it has to be.
别拦我
Get out of my way.
卡尔
Carl!
去橱柜里拿几把手枪吧
Just grab some pistols from the closet.
但得快点 马上就得出发了
But hurry. We've gotta go now.
卡尔
Carl!
该死的
Damn it!
求你了 求你了
Please, please.
不 不要 求你了 不要
No, no, please… Oh! No!
别打了 求你了
Please, don't. Oh! Please.
求你了
Please!
卡尔 卡尔
Carl! Carl!
你要是回不来了怎么办
What happens if you don't come back?
我要怎样继续撑下去
How am I supposed to live with that?
我到底该怎么办啊
What the hell am I supposed to do?
无论如何都要活下去
Just survive somehow.
我们做好保护这里的准备了
We're ready to protect this place.
而救世军清楚这一点
and the Saviors know it.
所以他们才会抓尤金
That's why they grabbed Eugene.
听着 这事没有商量的余地
Look, it's not up for discussion.
那你只能冲着我脸上来一拳
Then you're just gonna have to punch me in the face.
再把我绑起来一次
and tie me up again.
因为只有那样才能阻止我
'Cause that's what it's gonna take to stop me.
上车吧
Go on.
每个岗哨24小时都有人轮班
We have 24-hour shifts set up on each of the watchtowers,
每个站岗的人都全副武装 做好了准备
each one of them fully supplied and ready.
万一这里失守了
In the case that we're incurred upon,
我们安排好了司机
we have drivers assigned,
撤离以及牵制计划
evacuation and distraction,
集合点也商量好了
and the rendezvous we discussed.
无论出现什么紧急情况
In the event of any emergency,
我的首要任务都是保护朱迪斯
my first priority is Judith.
我不会辜负你的
I will not fail you.
你放心让我负责亚历山大的守卫吗
Are you comfortable leaving me in charge of Alexandria's defense?
放心
Yes.
瑞克
Hey, Rick.
假如救世军真的攻过来了…
If the Saviors do show up…
我也不知道
I don't know,
我在想 假如尚有余地的话
I'm thinking, if it's not too late,
我们要不要试图和他们谈判
should we try and make some kind of deal?
让他们等我回来
Tell them to wait for me.
我跟他们好好谈
I got a deal for them.
出发吧
Let's go.
卡萝尔
Carol?
我告诉过你别来了
I told you not to come.
好像我会听你的一样
And I'm gonna start listening to you real soon.
来 我看看
Here, let me see.
这是做什么
What is this?
这是我们准备拿你杀鸡儆猴
This is us about to make an example out of you.
给谁看
To who?
我的人…
My people…
图书馆里的所有人都死了
everyone at the library, they're dead.
《行尸走肉》
我们会到的
We're gonna get there.
山顶寨的医生
The doctor at the Hilltop,
他会让你好转的
he's gonna make things better.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我们所经历的一切 都是一起挺过来的
Everything we've done, we've done together.
我们一起来到这里 如今大家也都还在
We got here together and we're still here.
发生了许多事 但我们总能解决
Things have happened, but it's always worked out for us.
因为我们一直同舟共济
'cause it's always been all of us.
所以我知道
That's how I know.
只要我们在一起
'Cause as long as it's all of us,
就能战胜一切
we can do anything.
是行尸
It's a walker.
它很难搞
It's hard to get.
我本打算去杀它 但流血太多了
I was going to, but I was too busy bleeding.
按住伤口会好些 但还是需要缝针
Pressure should help, but you need stitches,
要用抗生素才不会感染
antibiotics to make sure you don't get an infection.
马上要天黑了
Be dark in a few hours.
我四处检查一下 确保能安全过夜
I'll walk the camp, make sure we're safe for the night.
天一亮我们就往回走
And at dawn, we will head back,
找人帮你缝针
get you some help.
好吗
Okay?
不
No.
他娘的
What the bitch?
怎么了
What?
有敌人
Enemy close.
要上吗
We doing this?
不
No.
这个人属于一个不听话的团队
He's someone who was with a whole lot of someones who didn't listen.
我们可以谈交易
We can make a deal.
就在这儿 就现在
right here, right now.
没错 是可以
That's right, we can.
把所有东西都交出来
Give us all your stuff.
我们可能得杀你们一个人
We'll probably have to kill one of you.
这是规矩没办法
That's just the way it is,
但之后我们可以开始谈
but then we can start moving forward on business.
只要你们乖乖听话
All you have to do is listen.
是啊…
Yeah…
你的条件我们不接受
that deal's not gonna work for us.
其实我还打算让你们把东西都交出来
Fact is, I was about to ask for all of your stuff,
但我不想杀你们中任何一人
only I'm thinking I don't have to kill any of you.
不想再杀了
Any more of you.
抱歉 必须按我说的办
Sorry, my deal is the only deal.
不讲价
We don't negotiate.
那我和我的人这就走
Me and my people are leaving.
好吧 朋友
Okay, friend.
去你们的目的地还不容易吗
Plenty of ways to get to where you're going.
你想让今天变成你的死期吗
You want to make today your last day on Earth?
不想
No,
但你提到了也好
but that is a good thing to bring up.
想想吧
Think about it.
万一今天是你的死期呢
What if it's the last day on Earth for you?
你所爱的人的死期
For someone you love?
万一真是这样呢
What if that's true?
或许你该对车上的人更好些
Maybe you should be extra nice to those people in that RV,
因为谁知道呢…
'cause you never know…
说没就没了
Just like that.
对彼此好一点
Be kind to each other.
就像你说的…
Like you said…
把今天当成最后一天来过
like it was your last day on Earth.
你也是
You do the same.
你为什么不留在家里守着
Why didn't you stay back and help guard the place?
我欠她的
I owe her.
那你为什么来
Why did you come?
我欠他们的
I owe them.
罗格朗路比较近
Logrun Road's a straight shot.
我们需要能见度
We want visibility.
这里 希尔顿路符合条件
There, you got it on Shelton.
高尔夫球场 乡村俱乐部 坡地地形
Golf course, country clubs, sloping terrain.
不会中埋伏 很远就能发现敌人
No bum rush from the bogeyman. We'd see them from a good piece.
这样会多走三分之一的路
It is a longer trip by a third,
但是周围一览无余 比较安全
but we'd get the scenic safety of clear-cut dingles and glens.
你是认真的吗
You're being serious, right?
比恶疾还真
As coronary thrombosis.
- 选好路线了吗 - 是的
- You got a route? - Yeah.
出发吧
Let's go.
不只我一个人
Wasn't just me.
瑞克也出来找你了
Rick came looking, too.
达里尔 还有其他人
Daryl, some of the others…
他们原本也会来的
They would've.
他们在知道你的事之前就出去了
They were gone before they even knew about you.
出去了
Gone?
我们回去时 他们也该回去了
They'll be back by the time we are.
也许已经回去了 等消息呢
Probably back already, wondering.
你以为我是在胡闹吗
You think I'm being dramatic here?
你真以为你找到这里
Do you really think you could just come here.
说让我回去 事情就解决了吗
and tell me to come back and that's how it'll go?
他们 你的伙伴
Those people, your people,
他们很在意你
they care about you.
这我知道 我也很在意他们
I know they do. And I care about them.
所以我才不能回去
That's why I can't be there.
所以你才必须回去
That's why you have to be there.
你真的不懂吗
Do you really just not get it?
在经历了这么多事之后
After everything that's happened.
如果你有在意的人 就会想保护他们
If you care about people, there are people to protect,
为他们而杀戮
there are people that you will kill for.
如果你不想杀戮
If you don't want to kill…
或不能再杀戮下去
or if you can't…
那就必须离开他们
then you have to get away from them.
两者不可兼得
You do not get both.
你应该懂的
You…you should know that.
不 人才是最重要的
No, everything's about people.
没了人的人生一文不值
Everything in this life that's worth a damn,
这就是我所知道的
that's what I know.
你独自出走
And out here on your own…
必死无疑
you'll die.
那就让我死吧
Then let me die.
不 我不能那么做
No, I can't do that.
这可不是你说了算 快走吧
It's not your decision. Just go.
我不会离开你的
I'm not leaving you.
我让你走
I said go.
求你了 走吧
Please, just go.
如果你有在意的人
If you care about anyone…
那就有代价 摩根 你要付出代价的
There is a price, Morgan, and you're gonna pay it.
我付过 今后付不起了
I have, and I can't anymore.
你觉得我们能做到吗
Think we could do it?
什么事
What?
格伦和玛姬做的事
What they did, Glenn and Maggie?
只想问问你能做到吗
Just asking if you could do that.
如果你在做那样的大事
If you're doing something as big as that…
如果那就是生活
if that's living.
你能吗
Could you?
能
Yeah.
我能
I could.
就现在
Now.
就想让你知道
Just so you know.
贱疯子
Bitch nuts.
我们要抵抗吗
We making our stand?
是的 了结他们
Yeah, we end it.
不 现在不要
No, not now.
他们是以逸待劳 早做好了准备
They've been waiting. They're ready.
我们一个人开车的情况下
With one of us behind the wheel,
是5对16
that's five on 16.
我们要按对我们有利的方法来
We're gonna play it our way, how we want it.
对吧
Right?
对
Right.
好 慢点退
All right, go slow.
卡萝尔
Carol?
走吧
Let's go.
还有多少油
How are we on gas?
一半
Half a tank.
走之前我还多装了几罐
I pulled some more cans before we left.
刚刚那些不是第一次拦路的人
Those weren't the same men who blocked the road the first time.
同样的装备 不同的战士
Same outfit, different soldiers.
他们人多
They got numbers.
我们继续开 送她到那里
We keep driving, we get her there.
肯定会到的
We will.
就算不得不灭掉他们所有人 也要送到
If we have to shove each and every one of them up their own asses.
我们不能开过去
We can't go through it.
不能拿房车冒险
Can't risk the RV.
你坐在驾驶座上 以防万一
You stay behind the wheel, just in case.
我们来开路
We'll clear it.
让它们这样手拉手要很多人才能完成
Putting together a red rover like that takes people.
很多很多人
A lot of them.
来吧 动手吧
Come on, let's do this.
爸
Dad.
那是米琼恩的
That's Michonne's.
那是达里尔的
That's Daryl's.
回房车 快
Get back to the RV! Go!
发动
Start it up!
那什么声音
What's that sound?
车底盘可能中弹了
Undercarriage could've caught a bullet.
或者是变速器出问题了 也可能没事
Or could be transmission. It could be nothing.
他们刚刚是朝我们的脚开枪
They were firing at our feet.
他们封住了路 但并没有想拦住我们
They blocked the road, but they weren't trying to stop us.
他们希望我们走这个方向
They want us in this direction.
巴顿路是向北的
Barton Road takes us north,
但他们得知道我们想去北面
but they gotta know we wanna go north.
走米多斯路
Meadows.
稍微偏东一点
Could take us east a piece,
但我们可以绕回到梅休路
but we can get back on track on Mayhew.
我们还剩下三分之一的油
We're down to a third of a tank.
到下一站我们可以加油
We could top off at the next stop,
- 但之后就没油了 - 好
- but no refills after that. - All right.
她在发烧
She's burning up.
瑞克
Rick.
调头
Go back.
去哪
Where?
走
Come on.
不要 走开
No, get away.
不
No.
呼吸变得越来越困难
Each breath is getting harder.
我估计也快不行了
I probably don't have too many more in me.
所以我要好好利用每一口呼吸
So I'm gonna make each one count.
接下来会这样
So, here's how it's gonna go.
你躺在那 我会看着你慢慢死去
You're gonna lie there and I'm gonna watch you die slow,
就像之前在公路上我的朋友们那样
just like my friends did back on that road.
我也会这样
Just like I'm gonna.
看看谁会赢 贱人
Let's see who wins, bitch.
看到了吗
You see that?
这样开头不错吧
That's a pretty good start, huh?
我们快到了吗
Are we close?
是的 马上就到了
Yeah, we're… we're getting there.
刚才 我听到了枪声
Were there… I heard shots.
是的 是救世军 不过他们都走了
Yeah, the Saviors, but they're gone.
是我们走了
We are.
我们会把你送到的
We're gonna get you there.
我知道
I know.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
孩子会没事的
The baby's gonna be okay.
现在还没到头 没有结束
This isn't it. This isn't it.
你还有很多日子呢
There's more.
你会好好活下去的
There's gonna be more.
我相信你 瑞克
I believe in you, Rick.
你笑什么 贱人
What do you got to smile about, bitch?
你什么毛病
What the hell's wrong with you?
我没有毛病
There's nothing wrong with me.
我就要死了 所以
I'm gonna die, so…
我不会有任何毛病了
there's nothing wrong with me anymore.
你觉得你苦受够了吗
You think you've suffered enough now?
不 估计还没有
No, probably not.
老天
Oh, God.
怎么 就这么完事了吗
What, are you done?
除非你现在杀了我 不然我不会死
Unless you kill me now, I'm not gonna die!
你快做决定
You decide!
世界不会做决定 只能你自己决定
The world doesn't decide! You decide!
你不能说走就走
You don't get to walk away.
还能得偿所愿
and get what you want!
住手
Stop.
放下枪
Drop it.
你能活着离开
You can survive this.
你可以的
You can.
放下枪
Drop it.
拜托
Please.
不
No.
你能让我好好死吗
Would you please just let me go?
你还不能死
It's not your time.
你会熬过去的
You are gonna come back from this.
发生什么事了
What happened here?
我找到你的马了
I found your horse.
也找到我的朋友了
Found my friend, too.
她需要帮助
She needs help.
那就让我们来帮你
Then let's get you some help.
这些踪迹
These tracks…
说明他们不光人多
they would indicate they not only have people,
还有大型武器装备
but some big-ass toys and capabilities.
表明我们陷在齐脖深的屎坑里
What it indicates is we are neck-deep up shit creek.
嘴还都大张着
with our mouths wide open.
- 别开枪 - 我可以试着打断链子
- Don't. - I can try and break the chain.
没用的
It won't work.
- 我可以试试 - 没用的
- I can try. - It won't work.
我们需要保留子弹
And we need the bullets.
你有好好对待你的人吧
You're treating your people good, right?
把今天当成最后一天来过
Like it was your last day on Earth?
或者是他们中某人的最后一天
Or maybe one of theirs?
你最好快走
You better go.
这里会很热的
It's gonna get hot.
去你们的目的地吧
You go get where you're going.
走吧 快走
Go, go.
上车
Get on.
我们怎么办
So, what's the play?
她需要医生
She needs a doctor.
北边还有两条路
There are two more routes north from here.
他们可能已经在路上等着我们了
They're probably waiting for us right now.
那他们就是在我们的前面 或者后面
So, they're ahead of us, probably behind us.
但他们其实并不是在等我们
But they're not waiting on us, per se,
他们在等这辆破车
they're waiting on this rust bucket.
但他们并不知道
And they don't know.
这辆破车里实时的人数
the moment-to-moment occupancy of said rust-bucket.
而且太阳马上下山了
And the sun sets soon.
这是最后一桶了
That's the last of it.
如果路上遇到车 就吸出汽油
If you see a car, try to siphon the gas.
除此之外 保持前进
Other than that, you keep moving.
我要让他们以为我们在配合着玩他们的游戏
I'll have them thinking we're playing their game.
一关接着一关 一级接着一级
All phases of the turn, level after level,
一步接着一步 我会骗得他们团团转
move after move, I'll keep them spun.
我向你保证 我会做到的
I assure you, I will.
我有东西要给你
I got something for you.
是个配方 不是西班牙冻汤的
It's a recipe, and it ain't gazpacho.
如何从零开始制造子弹
How to Build Bullets 101.
亚伯拉罕可以带你去那个地方 以防万一
Abraham can show you where, just in case.
谢谢你
Thank you for this.
谢谢你做的一切
For all of it.
有你在我们很幸运
We're lucky you're here.
我就勉强同意你这话吧
I won't argue with that.
踩油门稳一点
You go steady on the pedal.
别开得太猛
You don't make that thing gulp.
你怎么从来都没有让我开过卡车呢
How come you never let me drive the truck?
我以为你不会开车
I didn't think you could do it.
我错了
I was wrong.
你是个生存者
You're a survivor.
你一直都是
You always were.
我们只是以前不知道罢了
We just didn't know it.
我和你都没意识到
Me and you both.
谢谢你
Thank you.
亚伦 求你了
Aaron, please.
让我走路吧
Just let me walk it.
放松
Relax.
还有几英里就到了
Just a few more miles.
我听见我们走的时候你和她说的话了
I heard what you told her when we were leaving.
我们的确可以战胜一切
We can do anything,
因为我们会做一切必要的事
'cause we'll do anything we need to do.
以前是 以后也是
We have and we will.
丹妮斯身上发生的事
What happened to Denise,
我不允许再发生在任何人身上
I'm not gonna let anybody die like that again.
- 儿子… - 怎么了
- Son… - What?
走 快走
Go! Go!
很好
Good.
你们成功了
You made it.
欢迎来到你们的目的地
Welcome to where you're going.
我们要收走你们的武器
We'll take your weapons.
就现在
Now.
- 我们可以谈… - 不用谈了
- We can talk about… - We're done talking.
该听话了
Time to listen.
这是你的 对吧
That's yours, right?
没错 就是你的
Yeah, it's yours.
好了
Okay.
把她放下来 你们都跪下
Let's get her down and get you all on your knees.
好多事要办
Lots to cover.
等下
Hold up.
我们自己来
We got it.
可以 可以
Sure, sure.
你们得跪下
Gonna need you on your knees.
再带一个出来 立刻
Let's get you another one. Right now.
- 德怀特 - 来了
- Dwight! - Yeah.
快点
Chop-chop.
来吧
Come on.
带你见见人
You got people to meet.
玛姬
Maggie?
跪下
On your knees!
好啊
All right!
都到齐了
We got a full boat.
见见我们头儿
Let's meet the man.
吓尿裤子了吗
Pissing our pants yet?
好家伙 我觉得快了
Boy, do I have a feeling we're getting close.
没错
Yep.
马上就要屁滚尿流了
It's gonna be pee-pee pants city here real soon.
你们这些混蛋谁是头儿
Which one of you pricks is the leader?
是这人
It's this one.
他是头儿
He's the guy.
你就是瑞克 对吧
You're Rick, right?
我是尼根
I'm Negan.
你杀了我的手下 我可不太高兴
And I do not appreciate you killing my men.
而且 我派人
Also, when I sent my people.
去替我的手下报仇
to kill your people for killing my people,
你又杀了我更多手下
you killed more of my people.
不厚道
Not cool.
你都不知道
You have no idea.
你干的事儿有多不厚道
how not cool that shit is.
不过我想你马上就要知道了
But I think you're gonna be up to speed shortly.
没错
Yeah.
你马上就会很后悔跟我作对
You are so gonna regret crossing me in a few minutes.
你一定会的
Yes, you are.
瑞克 无论你做什么
You see, Rick, whatever you do,
无论什么情况
no matter what,
你都不该挑战新世界的秩序
you don't mess with the new world order.
我来告诉你新世界的秩序是什么
And the new world order is this,
非常非常简单
and it's really very simple.
所以即便你蠢 你也很可能确实蠢
So, even if you're stupid, which you very may well be,
你也能懂
you can understand it.
准备好了吗
You ready?
开始了 注意听
Here goes. Pay attention.
把你的东西给我
Give me your shit…
否则我就杀了你
or I will kill you.
今天就像是自我介绍日啊
Today was career day.
我们投入了很多
We invested a lot.
好让你们知道我是谁 我能做出什么事
so you would know who I am and what I can do.
你们现在都要替我工作了
You work for me now.
你们得到任何东西 都要上交给我
You have shit, you give it to me.
那就是你们的工作
That's your job.
我知道你们一时间很难接受这事
Now, I know that is a mighty big, nasty pill to swallow,
但你们最终一定会接受的
but swallow it you most certainly will.
你称霸一方
You ruled the roost.
建造了安全窝
You built something.
你们以为自己很安全
You thought you were safe.
我理解的
I get it.
但是世界已经失序
But the word is out.
你们并不安全
You are not safe.
一点都不安全
Not even close.
实际上 你们已经完蛋了
In fact, you are pegged,
如果你们不照我说的做 就更完蛋了
more pegged if you don't do what I want.
我想要的 就是你们一半的东西
And what I want is half your shit.
如果那太多了
And if that's too much,
你们可以制造 搜寻或盗窃更多的
you can make, find, or steal more,
迟早都得补上
and it'll even out sooner or later.
这就是你们现在的生存方式了
This is your way of life now.
你们越反抗 就越艰难
The more you fight back, the harder it will be.
所以 如果有人敲你家的门
So, if someone knocks on your door…
你就得让我们进去
…you let us in.
那扇门是属于我们的
We own that door.
你如果敢阻止我们
You try to stop us.
我们就把那扇门撞烂
and we will knock it down.
听明白了吗
You understand?
怎么 没有答复吗
What, no answer?
你们不会真的以为 你们不接受惩罚
You don't really think that you were gonna get through this.
就能逃过这一劫吧
without being punished, now, did you?
我并不想杀你们
I don't want to kill you people.
我想从一开始就说清楚这一点
Just want to make that clear from the get-go.
我要你们替我工作
I want you to work for me.
如果你们死了 还怎么替我工作 对吧
You can't do that if you're dead, now, can you?
我才不会去种菜园子
I'm not growing a garden.
但是你们杀了我的人 杀了很多人
But you killed my people, a whole damn lot of them.
多到我无法接受了
More than I'm comfortable with.
因此 你们必须付出代价
And for that, for that you're gonna pay.
所以现在…
So, now…
我要打爆你们其中一个人
I'm gonna beat the holy hell outta one of you.
这个…
This…
名叫露西尔
this is Lucille,
她非常厉害
and she is awesome.
所有这一切 只是为了从你们当中
All this, all this is just so we can pick out.
挑出一个人来接受光荣的牺牲
which one of you gets the honor.
我可得把胡子好好刮一下
Ugh, I gotta shave this shit.
你拿走了我们的一把枪
You got one of our guns.
你拿走了我们的很多枪
You got a lot of our guns.
该死的 孩子 放松一点嘛
Shit, kid, lighten up.
至少稍微哭一下嘛
At least cry a little.
天啊
Jesus.
你看上去糟透了
You look shitty.
我现在就应该解脱你
I should just put you out of your misery right now.
不 不
No! No!
住手
Stop it!
天啊
God…!
不
Nope.
- 不 把他放回队伍中 - 不
- Nope, get him back in line. - No.
不
No.
别
Don't.
好吧 听着
All right, listen.
永远不准再那样做
Don't any of you do that again.
我会弄死你们 没有例外
I will shut that shit down, no exceptions.
第一次算了
First one's free.
你们很紧张 我懂
It's an emotional moment, I get it.
糟透了 不是吗
Sucks, don't it?
当你意识到自己屁都不知道的时候
The moment you realize you don't know shit.
这是你儿子 对吗
This is your kid, right?
这肯定是你儿子
This is definitely your kid.
- 别这样了 - 嘿
- Just stop this! - Hey!
别逼我杀了这个未来的连环杀手
Do not make me kill the little future serial killer.
别给我动手的借口
Don't make it easy on me.
我必须选个人
I gotta pick somebody.
每个人都在餐桌上 供我享用
Everybody's at the table waiting for me to order.
真是太难选了
I simply cannot decide.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
点
Eenie…
兵
meenie…
点
miney…
将
mo…
骑
catch…
虎
a tiger…
打
by…
仗
his toe.
点到
If…
哪里
he hollers…
哪里就上
let him go.
头
My mother…
破
told me…
血
to pick.
流
the very…
死
best one…
在
and you…
场
are…
上
it.
有人敢动或说话
Anybody moves, anybody says anything,
就把那孩子的另一只眼睛挖出来喂他父亲吃
cut the boy's other eye out and feed it to his father.
然后我们再开始
and then we'll start.
你可以呼吸
You can breathe,
你可以眨眼
you can blink,
你可以哭泣
you can cry.
见鬼 你们每个人都会那样的
Hell, you're all gonna be doing that.
看看
Look at that.
真有种
Taking it like a champ!
该死
Damn!